All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I will be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
The Fishman Pirates, led by Horty Jones and assisted by Vander Deccan, plot to overthrow King Neptune.
It's not long before the Straw Hats get pulled into the conflict, which results in Horty detaining Zorro, Usopp, and Brook.
My soul, it's aching!
Wait, that's it!
What's so funny?
My idea!
If I can't end her existence, then I'll just have to end everyone else's!
It's settled.
That boy sure gave me a lot of trouble, though.
We're leaving Hachi in your care, Kami!
Right!
Let us make haste, Megalone!
This drug of yours is fearsome indeed, Horty.
A surprising confession!
The truth behind the assassination of Otohime!
All right, we're almost to the plaza!
Keep up the pace, Megalone!
Hold on, Father!
Hey, I'm here, Jabal!
She made just a head!
It's him!
Hey, I'm here, Jabal!
You can't imagine how happy I am to see you!
Father!
Wait, we're coming!
Hold on!
Don't do it!
It's going to be okay!
What are you doing to me?
Stay away from her!
No!
And if you don't want this to get ugly, best to come quietly!
Let me go!
Please!
Ah!
Good!
Take her to Horty!
Ah!
No way!
Curse the lot of you!
Ah!
Now this is quite the side!
Prince Maboshi!
Prince Riyumoshi!
Prince Fugaboshi!
But how?
They're just a bunch of pirates, right?
The princes were winning, but then it was like they just fell apart!
Not good!
If they can't save the king, I don't think anyone can!
Let's go!
I wanna lay down some more boom, sir!
Yeah!
If I get any hotter, I'm gonna dry he out!
First the soldiers and ministers, then the royal family!
Truly there is no one left in this country who can oppose us now!
I can't believe how strong they are!
Please forgive us, father!
We failed!
Don't be ashamed!
And the strength that bested you is not truly their own!
It doesn't matter if it doesn't matter if it lets them take over the country!
Kill them already, Captain Horty!
Burn them alive!
No!
Impale them!
Oh yeah!
After all, that's the leaf they deserve!
If they wanna go inside with humans, then they can die without pride!
Come on!
Everybody came for a show!
Do it now!
Kill them now!
That's enough.
We haven't heard from Deccan,
which means that Shirohoshi
is still out there somewhere.
Once she comes for them,
we'll kill them all.
You leave our sister
out of this! She's not a
fighter like us! So she
isn't a threat to you, Horty Jones!
You honestly think I don't
know the truth about your little
sister?
She's the only one of you with true
power. She may be meek, but
she's far from helpless.
I want her gone most of all.
You monster!
Captain Horty!
Got a special delivery
for ya!
We didn't even need to fight!
We caught him in a trap!
SHIROHOSHI!
I'm sorry!
I wanted to save you!
There we go.
That was fast.
SHIROHOSHI!
In one fell swoop, we captured
the two I was most concerned about.
I knew I would win.
But not this easily.
All of this is my fault,
isn't it, Jinbei?
I'm so sorry! If I hadn't been so foolish,
then you wouldn't be in this mess!
What's done is done, child!
Don't cry!
Now, Jinbei, welcome.
I must say,
this does disappoint me a bit.
You used to be strong.
Then I guess we've both changed.
Look at you!
Why, you're nothing but a monster now!
They got boss Jinbei!
What's he even doing here?
Didn't he leave after he quit the warlords?
But I thought Princess Shirohoshi
was kidnapped by Straw Hat Luffy.
Did Jinbei rescue her only to get them both captured?
I was ready for a fight,
but I won't complain.
Everyone I needed is neatly gathered here,
just as planned.
Now, the only concern I have left...
is the Straw Hats.
Although...
I'm sure they're more than a little preoccupied
at the moment, trying to find a way
into the palace.
I assume they'll come here after they discover
their friends are dead.
And once they do...
we'll be ready.
That...
is my army.
30,000 slaves we've captured this month.
All human too.
And then there's 70,000 fishmen...
trained in combat.
This...
is madness.
They're all from the fishmen district.
Or can't you tell?
Now behold...
100,000...
United Outlaws!
They're all from the fishmen district.
Or can't you tell?
Now behold...
100,000...
United Outlaws!
99,000!
100,000!
Doada bats bay!
13,000,000!
New
Just outside are women and children, more slaves, although they can't fight.
Well, I'm sure we can find a use for them later.
And they're only the first of many humans we will enslave in the coming days.
But as for you islanders, my men are in need of places to stay, so I expect you all to be accommodating by leaving your homes.
Whether you do that by running away or dropping dead makes no difference to me.
What a pathetic scene. You have no class, like a bunch of rowdy children.
You should quit while you're ahead. Horty, Jones.
It's been a long time, Charlie. Is there a reason you're here?
Yes, I wanted to deliver a message. While you're still at the height of your glory.
What did she just say?
I recently had a vision of the imminent destruction of our island. It was a fate brought on by a single man.
Oh yeah, I guess you could call this destruction. So was it me that you saw in your prophecy?
No.
The man who will destroy Fishman Island is Straw Hat Luffy.
That can't be.
Oh, but I'm afraid it can. That said, I don't know how.
The means, well, there's still a mystery to me.
What exactly's your point?
My point is, it's not you.
Fine. I'll spell it out.
No matter what you think you're accomplishing, the person who decides the fate of this island isn't you.
It's a human.
Hear that? Madam Charlie's visions are always accurate.
Yeah. That means Horty will never be in control of Fishman Island.
No matter what he does.
No matter what he does, he will never be in control of Fishman Island.
Charlie, no!
How could he do that?
What a load of crap.
What did you hope to accomplish?
Huh?
Come on, let's hear it!
Charlie, you know I'm nothing like your brother.
It's true. I looked up to him a lot when I was a kid.
That's how everybody was with Arlong back then.
However, that changed when we acquired real power.
We didn't take the name Arlong Pirates out of reverence to him.
All we needed was a flag to rally behind.
A symbol to unite people like us.
And now that symbol has served its purpose,
we have surpassed Arlong in strength and ambition alike.
There's only one man capable of destroying this country
and building something better.
And that's me, you got it?
Otherwise, you wouldn't be here, right?
You see, this is power.
Because my followers have faith in change.
It's taken 10 years, but it's time that we finished
what I began so long ago.
And you know what started it?
The death of Queen Otahime.
Yes, that's right.
I've got a little secret.
Wanna hear?
When she was killed,
the one who shot her...
was me!
That can't be true!
Oh no!
The human!
But what about him?
We saw him!
I can't believe in all these years,
you idiots never figured it out!
Can't ya?
The day before,
I had made a deal.
I got no clue who you are.
I don't really care.
As long as you got the money to pay me,
I'll do whatever it is you want.
That's what I'm talking about!
Consider this a down payment.
I'll give you the other half
after you finish the job.
Mister,
you have yourself a deal.
Just this alone
is enough to keep me drunk for a week.
So, what do you want me to do?
Don't worry,
it's quite simple.
Even a child could do it.
That said,
do not let anyone see you.
And when the moment came...
Get away!
Fire!
We need water!
Hurry!
Secure the royal family!
Quick!
Put it out!
Queen Urohime has been shot!
Hey!
Hurry up and pay me already!
I torched all those signatures
like you told me to,
so I've earned my cut.
Still,
I gotta get out of here
before those guards come looking for me.
What's the big idea?
Humans are so stupid.
Oh, damn it!
It was a human!
A human assassinated our queen!
This is what humans are capable of!
Killing in cold blood!
And that was all it took to fool every single one of you!
No!
Damn you!
He killed our queen!
Hardy,
you bastard!
No!
Dude!
Mother, please!
Hardy!
Stop it right now!
She was a nuisance!
Right, Shirohoshi?
Always telling us to forget about revenge.
And then begging us all to try and be friends with the humans.
Worst of all, she was so close to getting what she wanted.
I knew just murdering her wasn't going to cut it anymore.
It wasn't enough!
I had to kill her dream.
Only then would your mother truly die.
Shut your mouth!
Leave her alone!
How dare you!
And so, I came up with a strategy.
I would use her death to my advantage.
With that one simple act, I could change the direction this country was moving in to my favor.
I rekindled the hatred, the fear, how people thought they'd forgotten.
Then, just like that, the islanders' hopes died alongside their queen.
That's it.
One human.
That was all that it took.
If I made one of them my scapegoat, I knew our people would feel so angry and so betrayed that they would never question it.
As it turned out, it wasn't even that difficult.
Every person on the island bought into it exactly like I wanted.
Can't start a revolution without a few sacrifices.
Right, Princess?
Even in her death, your mother changed the island by turning the humans into villains once more.
And yet, it wasn't them.
No!
It was her own subject!
The fish man standing in front of you!
I did it!
I killed her!
Because it was necessary!
I knew you did it!
Shiro Hoshi!
What did you say?
A long time ago, the people of Fishman Island came together to build a mysterious giant ship.
They called it Noah.
The reason why they did this is unknown.
Hence the mysterious part, obviously.
Anyhow, it's nothing but a forgotten piece of the past until I touch it with my right hand.
Captain Deccan, what are you up to exactly?
Guys, what's going on?
It's over.
The pain in my heart will never go away.
I suspect.
It's moving!
I don't know what to do!
Just run!
I've thrown Noah at Shiro Hoshi.
So now...
I'm out of here!
Wait!
This ship is half the size of Fishman Island!
That means when this thing reaches the princess, it won't just crush her.
Everything will be destroyed!
You can't run from me anymore, princess!
From now until the end of time, you can live on right here in my heart, but only there!
Goodbye, my dear!
I'm out of here!
Happyin' doin' finally, cassette game handed for me!
Why is the pilot being ruined for me?!
All this thing is, no?
That's so cool!"
It won't just crush her!
Everything will be destroyed!
You can't run from me anymore, princess!
From now, until the end of time, you can live on right here in my heart, but only there!
Good bye, my darling!
I hope you burn into hell like my love burned for you!
And good riddance to Fishman Island!
Ha-ha!
Even in the face of Horty's cruelty,
Shirahoshi holds true to her mother's dying wish.
The burden she carried for 10 years
is finally brought to light
as the Ryugu kingdom lies on the brink of destruction.
The people of Fishman Island,
recalling Madame Charlie's prophecy,
call out to a man who may bring ruin and rebirth alike.
On the next One Piece, Shirahoshi's tears,
Luffy finally shows up!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!